Jonukuti Akhilarjun

Email: jonukutiakhilarjun@gmail.com | Mobile: 6281511132

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

I am a highly skilled web developer with over **1** year of experience in **HTML**, **CSS**, **JavaScript,TypeScript,Go and PHP**. I have knowledge of popular frameworks/libraries such as **React and MaterialUI** and experience with REST APIs and MVC frameworks.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages : JavaScript, TypeScript, Python, Go, PHP, Java, HTML, CSS

Frameworks: React.js, Express, Node.jsLibraries: MaterialUI, Redux, React RouterDatabases: MySQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB

Dev Tools : Visual Studio Code, Git

EXPERIENCE

Software Developer

June 2023 - Present

Location: Hyderabad, Telangana

Sureify Hybrid – Hyderabad, Telangana

- Designed and developed dynamic and responsive websites using React, Typescript, JavaScript, Node and PHP
 Worked with REST APIs to retrieve and display data from databases
- Worked with MVC frameworks to develop robust and scalable backends
- Troubleshot and fixed bugs and issues in the backend to ensure smooth operation of the applications

Software Developer (Intern)

Feb 2023 - June 2023

Sureify

- Gained extensive knowledge in **Web Development** during the internship
- Developed a polling Application using React which provides a platform for creating, managing, and analyzing polls in real-time

Chegg Expert During College

Chegg

Provided comprehensive solutions in CS to hundreds of students globally with expert answers and step-by-step
instructions

EDUCATION

Sreenidhi Institute Of Science and Technology

Bachelor of Technology - Computer Science

Hyderabad, Telangana Aug 2019 – Jul 2023

PROJECTS

Authenticated Layout for Insurance Portals

React.js,Redux,MUI,NodeJs,Nestjs, PHP, MySQL,Git

- * Created an authenticated layout for insurance portal using **React with Material-UI (MUI) and TypeScript**, ensuring secure and user-friendly access.
- * Optimized website for speed and user experience

App Tracker for Insurance Portal

React.js,Redux,MUI,NodeJs,Nestjs, PHP, MySQL,Git

- * Used to monitor and manage the application status of users within the insurance domain.
- * It provides real-time updates on the progress of insurance applications, ensuring transparency and efficiency throughout the process.

ACHIEVEMENTS

• Star Employee of the Quarter